Koushik Nimmala

Bloomington, Indiana, United States

njkoushik9@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/koushik-nimmala-jay

Summary

My name is Koushik Nimmala, and I am from India, pursuing a major in Business Management at Indiana University. I opted for this course mainly because the bachelor's in management program will provide me with the competitive edge I need to succeed in the corporate world and equip me with transferable abilities that I can utilize in other facets of my life, such as planning, persuasion, and management. I am a dedicated and energetic guy with a passion for understanding intriguing real-world business. Through my experiences in high school, college, and internships, I have developed my talents in leadership, time management, and analytical thinking. My goal is to flourish in business by using these abilities and encouraging innovation. This course will quickly make me a competent and active management professional.

Experience



Digital Marketing Intern

Naresh i Technologies

Jun 2021 - Present (2 years 9 months)

- Supported marketing team by writing and editing 100+ social media and email campaigns
- Bolstered blog content with attention to SEO and keyword research, helping drive total site traffic up
- Studied analytics in Google Search Console, identified low-performing content, and recommended solutions that improved content performance by an average of 34%

Graphic Designer Internship

FutureSkills Prime

Apr 2023 - Aug 2023 (5 months)

- Designing logos/identities, publications, folders, etc.
- Demonstrating proficient skills in Adobe programs.
- · Giving feedback on current website layouts.
- Skills Used Adobe Indesign, Illustrator, Photoshop. Google Drive.

→ Sports Marketing Intern

PUMA Group

Apr 2022 - Aug 2022 (5 months)

- Assisting with marketing strategles Organizing game day promotions Game day advertisement.
- Conducted market research to determine products target market and demographics of the target market in order to develop effective marketing.

Education



Indiana University Bloomington



Delhi Public School - India

High School Diploma, Business/Commerce, General Jun 2010 - Mar 2023

Skills

Marketing Support • Sports Industry • Endorsements • Adobe Creative Suite • Data Analysis • Web Content Writing • Social Media • Corporate Branding • Graphic Design • Adobe InDesign